<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Abouts on YMMOR</title>
    <link>https://ymmor-conferences.github.io/homepage/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Abouts on YMMOR</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>youremail@domain.com (YMMOR Committee)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>youremail@domain.com (YMMOR Committee)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 15:54:41 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://ymmor-conferences.github.io/homepage/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Committee</title>
      <link>https://ymmor-conferences.github.io/homepage/about/committee/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 15:54:41 +0200</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (YMMOR Committee)</author>
      <guid>https://ymmor-conferences.github.io/homepage/about/committee/</guid>
      <description>About Us The YMMOR-committee consists of young researchers that are interested in the continuation and further improvement of the conference format. Its purpose is the sustainability of the format independent of a particular institute or current conference organizers.
Becoming a member Every young researcher (PhD or early Postdoc) in the field of model order reduction is welcome to join the committee! Being a regular member does not come with any obligations, although you should of course try to attend the committee meetings which are held approximately 2-4 times per year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The conference format</title>
      <link>https://ymmor-conferences.github.io/homepage/about/conference_format/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>youremail@domain.com (YMMOR Committee)</author>
      <guid>https://ymmor-conferences.github.io/homepage/about/conference_format/</guid>
      <description>The key idea of YMMOR is to regularly bring together early career researchers that are working in Model Order Reduction and related topics. The focus of the conference is scientific exchange and networking in an informal atmosphere among PhD students, master students, and early postdocs. Therefore, participation by experienced researchers such as professors is not intended.
The conference takes place on a yearly basis. Every participant is usually expected to present his work in order to facilitate discussions.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
